[
  {
    "question": "ハイシー",
    "correct": "アスコルビン",
    "choices": [
      "ニトログリセリン",
      "コンドロイチンエステル",
      "アスコルビン",
      "イグラチモド"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ニチファーゲン",
    "correct": "グリチルリチングリシンメチオニン",
    "choices": [
      "プロパフェノン",
      "ピモベンダン",
      "アゼルニジピン",
      "グリチルリチングリシンメチオニン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "スイニー",
    "correct": "アナグリプチン",
    "choices": [
      "アナグリプチン",
      "グリメピリド",
      "エペリゾン",
      "エスシタロプラムシュウ"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "タケキャブ",
    "correct": "ボノプラザン",
    "choices": [
      "ボノプラザン",
      "レボセチリジン",
      "ベタキソロール",
      "ペントキシベリン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "トランサミン",
    "correct": "トラネキサム",
    "choices": [
      "トラマドール・アセトアミノフェン",
      "ジクロフェナク",
      "エスゾピクロン",
      "トラネキサム"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "シナール",
    "correct": "アスコルビンパントテンカルシウム",
    "choices": [
      "ピタバスタチンカルシウム",
      "ロスバスタチンカルシウム",
      "アスコルビンパントテンカルシウム",
      "アトルバスタチンカルシウム"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "アスパラ",
    "correct": "アスパラギンカルシウム",
    "choices": [
      "アスパラギンカルシウム",
      "アトルバスタチンカルシウム",
      "ピタバスタチンカルシウム",
      "ロスバスタチンカルシウム"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ビフロキシン",
    "correct": "リボフラビンピリドキシン",
    "choices": [
      "トラニラスト",
      "ピリドキシン",
      "カルテオロール",
      "リボフラビンピリドキシン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ユベラ",
    "correct": "トコフェロールエステル",
    "choices": [
      "クロルフェネシンカルバミンエステル",
      "トコフェロールエステル",
      "リボフラビンエステル",
      "トコフェロールニコチンエステル"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ノイロトロピン",
    "correct": "ワクシニアウイルス",
    "choices": [
      "ビマトプロスト",
      "センナ・センナ",
      "フルオシノロンアセトニド",
      "ワクシニアウイルス"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "スーグラ",
    "correct": "イプラグリフロジンプロリン",
    "choices": [
      "エスタゾラム",
      "イプラグリフロジンプロリン",
      "シベンゾリンコハク",
      "イソソルビド"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "デベルザ",
    "correct": "トホグリフロジン",
    "choices": [
      "エンタカポン",
      "エカベト",
      "レナリドミド",
      "トホグリフロジン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "セルベックス",
    "correct": "テプレノン",
    "choices": [
      "ドルゾラミド・チモロール",
      "テプレノン",
      "エストラジオール",
      "ジサイクロミン・アルミニウム"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "トピロリック",
    "correct": "トピロキソスタット",
    "choices": [
      "エパルレスタット",
      "フェブキソスタット",
      "トピロキソスタット",
      "ニトラゼパム"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ジャヌビア",
    "correct": "シタグリプチン",
    "choices": [
      "シタグリプチン",
      "アゼラスチン",
      "トラピジル",
      "アナストロゾール"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "アローゼン",
    "correct": "センナセンナ",
    "choices": [
      "タモキシフェン",
      "ロキシスロマイシン",
      "クレマスチン",
      "センナセンナ"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "リクシアナ",
    "correct": "エドキサバントシル",
    "choices": [
      "メトプロロール",
      "トスフロキサシントシル",
      "イコサペントエチル",
      "エドキサバントシル"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "トラディアンス",
    "correct": "エンパグリフロジンリナグリプチン",
    "choices": [
      "エンパグリフロジンリナグリプチン",
      "ドンペリドン",
      "スピロノラクトン",
      "トランドラプリル"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ベルソムラ",
    "correct": "スボレキサント",
    "choices": [
      "スボレキサント",
      "シメチジン",
      "ラタノプロスト・チモロール",
      "エキセメスタン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "スージャヌ",
    "correct": "シタグリプチンイプラグリフロジンプロリン",
    "choices": [
      "フルスルチアミン",
      "シタグリプチンイプラグリフロジンプロリン",
      "ラロキシフェン",
      "デュタステリド"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ツイミーグ",
    "correct": "イメグリミン",
    "choices": [
      "メコバラミン",
      "ドキサゾシンメシル",
      "イメグリミン",
      "オキシブチニン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ワイテンス",
    "correct": "グアナベンズ",
    "choices": [
      "トラニラスト",
      "ヒドロコルチゾン・フラジオマイシン",
      "グアナベンズ",
      "デキストロメトルファン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "グーフィス",
    "correct": "エロビキシバット",
    "choices": [
      "ビペリデン",
      "メコバラミン",
      "エロビキシバット",
      "ブチルスコポラミン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ツートラム",
    "correct": "トラマドール",
    "choices": [
      "トレミフェン",
      "プロカテロール",
      "デキサメタゾンプロピオンエステル",
      "トラマドール"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ペリアクチン",
    "correct": "シプロヘプタジン",
    "choices": [
      "フルタミド",
      "シプロヘプタジン",
      "ゲフィチニブ",
      "ニトログリセリン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "フォシーガ",
    "correct": "ダパグリフロジンプロピレングリコール",
    "choices": [
      "アモキシシリン",
      "ダパグリフロジンプロピレングリコール",
      "ジエノゲスト",
      "グリベンクラミド"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ベタニス",
    "correct": "ミラベグロン",
    "choices": [
      "トラマドール・アセトアミノフェン",
      "ミラベグロン",
      "アルクロメタゾンプロピオンエステル",
      "スクラルファート"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "パルモディア",
    "correct": "ペマフィブラート",
    "choices": [
      "ペマフィブラート",
      "アンブロキソール",
      "フェノフィブラート",
      "ベザフィブラート"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "チラーヂン",
    "correct": "レボチロキシン",
    "choices": [
      "レボチロキシン",
      "レボフロキサシン",
      "ジフェニドール",
      "シクロスポリン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "グルベス",
    "correct": "ミチグリニドカルシウムボグリボース",
    "choices": [
      "ミチグリニドカルシウムボグリボース",
      "ボグリボース",
      "アズレンスルホン",
      "オキシコナゾール"
    ]
  }
]